city-journal.org 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy | City Journal

May 1, 2018 | New York, City

_Effective:_ May 1, 2018

Welcome to City Journal website (the “Site”), owned and operated by the Manhattan Institute (“we,” “us,” or “our”). The Site is designed to serve as an online magazine resource for parties interested in City Journal and the Manhattan Institute. The following Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and share information you provide to us through your use of the Site or any other Manhattan Institute/City Journal apps or websites linking to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”). By using or visiting the Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, effective immediately upon posting on the Services. Please check this page of the Services periodically for such changes. Your continued use of the Services following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. You agree that the information that we gather now will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

_Information We Collect_

Both information you provide and information collected automatically can be used in marketing communications unless users request removal of said data.

Information You Provide.

When you visit the Services, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. “Personal information” (as the term is used in this Privacy Policy) consists of information such as your name, mailing address, phone number or email address. We use the personal information you provide to us to answer your questions, provide you with the information you requested, or as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent. We may also use your demographic information to tailor the Services to you and for internal purposes such as analytics to improve the Services.

Except as described below (see “Information We Share”), we do not share your personal information with any third parties except (1) if we determine that an applicable law, regulation or legal process requires it; (2) in response to a request from law enforcement personnel; or (3) if we determine that we need to share such information with others to protect the Services and/or to protect or enforce our rights.

Information Collected Automatically

We also may collect certain information automatically when you visit the Services, including:

  * Your browser type and operating system;
  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area;
  * Sites you visited before and after visiting the Services;
  * Pages you view and links you click on within the Services;
  * Information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies;
  * Information about your interactions with e-mail messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded; and
  * Standard server log information.

We may use cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies to automatically collect this information. Cookies are small bits of information that are stored by your computer’s web browser. Pixel tags are very small images or small pieces of data embedded in images, also known as “web beacons” or “clear GIFs,” that can recognize cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, a description of the page where the pixel tag is placed, and similar information from your computer or device. By using the Services, you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain online products, services, or features on the Services.

We also may allow third parties to place and read their own cookies, web beacons, Local Shared Objects, and similar technologies to collect information through the Services. For example, our third-party service providers may use these technologies to collect information that helps us with traffic measurement, research, analytics, and/or advertising.

_Information We Share_

Personal Information. We may share your personal information with our corporate parents, subsidiaries, or other affiliated entities, as well as with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as hosting the Services, managing our databases, or performing analyses. In addition, if we sell all or part of City Journal and/or the Manhattan Institute, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your information — including personal information — to one or more third parties as part of that transaction. In addition we may share your personal information (1) if we determine that an applicable law, regulation or legal process requires it; (2) in response to a request from law enforcement personnel; or (3) if we determine that we need to share such information with others to protect the Services and/or to protect or enforce our rights.

Aggregated Information. We do not link our cookies or your IP address to any of your personal information. We may aggregate this information, and/or other information that does not describe or identify individual users, with that of other users and analyze it to improve the Services. We may share aggregated information with potential partners, advertisers, investors, content providers and customers in connection with the promotion of our services. However, this aggregated information does not include personal information.

Sharing on Social Networks. We have worked with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through our Services. For example, you can use third-party social networking services, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, and others, to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those social networking services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services. These third-party social networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies. If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those social networking services.

_Other Practices_

No Absolute Safeguards. Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of your information (personally identifiable or otherwise) due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

Children. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13.

Third Parties. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties that have websites linked to the Services. For instance, we may provide tools allowing you to share articles on the Services through services such as Facebook or Twitter. If you click on a link or use such tools, the privacy policies of the website that you link to will govern the use of your information by that website’s operator. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of third parties with respect to their use of your information. Accordingly, make sure you are aware of, and comfortable with, the privacy policies of any third-party websites you link to.

International Users.  _The Platform is hosted in and managed from the United States. United States data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction.  _ **By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States.**

Correct/Update Personal Information. If you would like to review, update, change, or delete information that we have collected from you, please send an email to [communications@manhattan-institute.org](mailto:communications@manhattan-institute.org) or write to: 52 Vanderbilt Avenue, 2nd Floor, New York, NY 10017.
